LWRGitHub.GitHub.io

— SF, CA - (415) 886-0145 - <u>LoganReynoldsLWR@gmail.com</u> — **Logan Reynolds**

Full-stack software engineer, UX/UI designer, game developer, & data Scientist. I always go above and beyond to ensure the job is done right the first time. Having been in these fields for some time now & done any projects in teams & alone I have the necessary experience to accomplish the job.

Key Skills:

- Expert: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Command Line & Terminal, Google Fonts, DOM, Git, GitHub, Adobe Photoshop, Sketch, Adobe Dreamweaver, Adobe Muse, NPM, Google AdSense, JSON, Local Storage, Wix, Go Daddy, WordPress, CI/CD, Wire Frames, jQuery, & Trello.
- Proficient: Node.js, P5*JS, Pug, AWS, Cloud 9, BitBucket, Heroku, Adobe Creative Cloud Suite, Google Analytics, Google Maps, Jade,
 & SQL.
- Novice: MediaElement.js, Express.js, Mongoose.js, Passport.js, Vimeo JS Player SDK, Python, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Sinatra, Erb files, Active Record, C#, Unity, Cloudflare, Popper.js, React.js, React Bootstrap, WebVTT, MongoDB, Phaser, GTW, GIF & SVG images, AJAX, Fetch API, REST API, AI, Twilio, Browserify, SEO, & SASS.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Software Engineer - Full-stack experience in projects that use continuous integration & continuous deployment. Knowledge of many frameworks languages, databases & different technologies. Ability to complete projects quickly & multitask. Having had many jobs in the field of software engineering and gone to many schools, I am an experienced candidate.

UX/UI Design - 10+ years expertise in creative tools that include Adobe suite (e.g., Photoshop, Dreamweaver), Sketch & more. Having studied UX design at DVC & many other schools, as well as having many jobs in the field, I have a high skill level in the area.

Game Development - Experience using game engines as well as vanilla game DEV. You will find that my UX/UI design skills are very handy when it comes to the look of the game. Having been a part of many game hackathons, taken classes in the field & attended many meetups, I am a well-rounded game developer.

Data Science - Ability to juggle multiple problems and projects using domain expertise, programming skills, and knowledge of mathematics and statistics to extract meaningful insights from data. On the job knowledge & education in this field is strong. Having used many languages to complete projects in this area my software engineering skills have served me well.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

2020 - present Intern, Software Engineer - UX/UI Design - Wordpress - stageIV.org e-commerce	SF, CA
2020 - present Intern, Software Engineer - UX/UI Design- Data Science - Dance4Healing.com	SF, CA
2019 - present Software Engineer - UX/UI Design - Game DEV - Data Science - Freelance	SF, CA
2018 - present UX/UI Design - Amazon KDP Publisher e-commerce	SF, CA

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Applied Computer Science Web/Mobile DEV Software Engineering Game DEV Coding Bootcamp Computer Science Studies UI/UX Design

Make School "Dominican University," SF, CA

Meda Mission Techies, SF, CA

Code Tenderloin, SF, CA

Noisebridge, SF, CA

Code The Dream, Durham, NC

Linda, Treehouse, Code Cademy, Khan Academy, Udacity, Online
Diablo Valley College, PleasantHill, CA